import { v4 as uuidv4 } from 'uuid';

export const digitalAgency = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How much did the first computer weigh?',
    answer: 'The very first computer ENIAC weighed over 27 tonnes and occupied 1800 square meters. About 3000 modern laptops fill the same amount of space.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 500 kg',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 27 t',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 987 kg',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 17 t',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'In what year the first SMS message was sent?',
    answer: 'December 3, 1992, was the day the first SMS message was sent. It happened in Great Britain, and it was the best wishes for the upcoming Christmas.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 1991',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 1992',
        isCorect: true,
      },
      
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 1993',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 1994',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What does WiFi stand for?',
    answer: 'Initially, WiFi was promoted with The Standard for Wireless Fidelity slogan. Then, the technology received its name – Wireless Fidelity, which was shortened to WiFi.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. White Fiddle',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Wicked Fiend',
        isCorect: false,
      },
      
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Wireless Fidelity',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Wife Fiduciary',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What is the origin of the word “Robot”?',
    answer: 'The word “robot” comes from the word “robota,” which means hard labor. The Czech writer Karel Čapek first used it in his sci-fi play “R.U.R.” (1920). In the play, it meant artificially created organic “people” used by humanity for hard and dangerous work.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Work, career',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Hard work, labor',
        isCorect: true,
      },
      
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Robotics',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Bio-organism, creating a person',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What kind of terminator model did Arnold Schwarzenegger play in the second movie "Terminator"?',
    answer: 'In the second part of the film Terminator, Arnold Schwarzenegger played a T-800 terminator robot. T-800 is the most massive series of terminators. And this is the first robot whose endoskeleton is covered with artificial skin identical to that of a human, making the T-800 indistinguishable from a human.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. T-1000',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. T-800',
        isCorect: true,
      },
      
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. T-600',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Cyberdyne Systems 101',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How much time Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin spent on the moon?',
    answer: 'On July 20, 1969, at 20:17:39 UTC, crew commander Neil Armstrong and the pilot Buzz Aldrin climbed out of the lunar module and descended onto the Sea of Tranquility. They stayed on the Moon surface for 21 hours, 36 minutes, and 21 seconds. All this time, command module pilot Michael Collins waited for them in lunar orbit.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 17 hours, 45 minutes, and 32 seconds',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 23 hours, 14 minutes, and 12 seconds',
        isCorect: false,
      },
      
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 19 hours, 38 minutes, and 28 seconds',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 21 hours, 36 minutes, and 21 seconds',
        isCorect: true,
      },
    ],
  },
];

export const binaryx = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'The first decentralized cryptocurrency was first released in...',
    answer: 'Bitcoin is the first decentralized cryptocurrency. It was first released as open-source software in January 2009. The cryptocurrency was invented by an unknown person or group of people using the name Satoshi Nakamoto.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 2006',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 2007',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 2008',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 2009',
        isCorect: true,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'The first commercial bitcoin transaction was for...',
    answer: 'On May 22, 2010, a man in Florida paid 10,000 bitcoin for two pizzas. This is generally recognized as the first commercial bitcoin transaction. At the time, 10,000 bitcoin was worth about $40, making one bitcoin “worth” a little less than half a cent. Today, if you had that much in bitcoin, it would be worth more than $350 million.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. iPhone',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Pizza',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Concert ticket',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. A cup of coffee',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What do you think of how many people use blockchain?',
    answer: 'Despite all the hype around bitcoin and blockchain, only 0.71% of the world’s population (65 million people) are involved in blockchain technology.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Less than 1% of the world population',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 2% of the world population',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 4% of the world population',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 7% of the world population',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'Let’s talk about tokenized assets. Which of these assets hasn’t been tokenized yet?',
    answer: 'Actually, there are various amounts of assets that can be tokenized. But towels haven’t been tokenized...yet.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Art',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Shares',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Towels',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Real estate',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'Which age group is most accepting of tokens?',
    answer: 'According to a KPMG report, the so-called “Generation Z” is the generation with the highest interest in tokens and tokenization - 83% of 18 to 24-year-olds see these things as part of their future.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 18 – 24 years',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 25 – 40 years',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 41 – 56 years',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Over 57 years',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'Which benefit of asset tokenization for businesses and investors?',
    answer: 'All of the mentioned benefits suit asset tokenization. To learn more about digital assets and tokenization visit Binaryx.com.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Joint ownership',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Liquidity',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Transparency',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Marketability',
        isCorect: true,
      },
    ],
  },
];

export const powercode = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'The first website went live on August 6, 1991. In what country?',
    answer: 'The first website ever made info.cern.ch went live on August 6, 1991. Its creator, Tim Berners-Lee, published there the description of the new World Wide Web technology that was based on the HTTP data transfer protocol, URI addressing system, and HTML hypertext markup language.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. USA',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. The Netherlands',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Switzerland',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Germany',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How many people on the planet have access to the internet?',
    answer: '4,05 billion out of about 7 billion people on the planet use the internet. In 2021, 45,4% of the population (about 3,3 billion) still have no access to the internet. The majority of them live in the least developed countries.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 4,05 billion',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 2,3 billion ',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 6,08 billion',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 5,7 billion',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What was the first YouTube video about?',
    answer: 'The very first video is the 18-second video of Jawed Karim at the San Diego Zoo that was published on YouTube on April 23, 2005, at 20:27 local time.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Steve Jobs iPhone introduction speech',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Jawed Karim, one of the PayPal developers, watches elephants at the zoo',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. A boy from Michigan takes a sandwich away from a raccoon',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Sergey Brin graduates from Stanford University',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How much time a day do all internet users spend on Facebook?',
    answer: 'Facebook users spend about 6 billion minutes on this social network. It’s about 35 minutes a day spent by each user.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. About 7M minutes',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. About 10B minutes',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. About 6B minutes',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. About 90M minutes',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How many products are sold on Amazon annually?',
    answer: 'Over 5 billion products are sold on Amazon each year. It’s more than 28 million buyers and over 3 million shipments per day.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Over 5 billion',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Over 7 billion',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Over 2 billion',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Over 10 billion',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What is the second most popular website?',
    answer: 'While Google is the most popular website, YouTube is in second place. YouTube is the world’s most popular resource for video entertainment, and no wonder it has such a high position. In fact, this position is supported by the fact that over 500 hours of video content are uploaded to the website each minute. Over 1 billion videos are watched daily.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Facebook',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Amazone',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. YouTube',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Wikipedia',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },
];

export const ease = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How much did the first computer weigh?',
    answer: 'The very first computer ENIAC weighed over 27 tonnes and occupied 1800 square meters. About 3000 modern laptops fill the same amount of space.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 500 kg',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 27 t',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 987 kg',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 17 t',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'In what year the first SMS message was sent?',
    answer: 'December 3, 1992, was the day the first SMS message was sent. It happened in Great Britain, and it was the best wishes for the upcoming Christmas.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 1991',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 1992',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 1993',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 1994',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What does WiFi stand for?',
    answer: 'Initially, WiFi was promoted with The Standard for Wireless Fidelity slogan. Then, the technology received its name – Wireless Fidelity, which was shortened to WiFi.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. White Fiddle',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Wicked Fiend',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Wireless Fidelity',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Wife Fiduciary',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What is the origin of the word “Robot”?',
    answer: 'The word “robot” comes from the word “robota,” which means hard labor. The Czech writer Karel Čapek first used it in his sci-fi play “R.U.R.” (1920). In the play, it meant artificially created organic “people” used by humanity for hard and dangerous work.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Work, career',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Hard work, labor',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Robotics',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Bio-organism, creating a person',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What kind of terminator model did Arnold Schwarzenegger play in the second movie "Terminator"?',
    answer: 'In the second part of the film Terminator, Arnold Schwarzenegger played a T-800 terminator robot. T-800 is the most massive series of terminators. And this is the first robot whose endoskeleton is covered with artificial skin identical to that of a human, making the T-800 indistinguishable from a human.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. T-1000',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. T-800',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. T-600',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Cyberdyne Systems 101',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How much time Neil Armstrong and Buzz Aldrin spent on the moon?',
    answer: 'On July 20, 1969, at 20:17:39 UTC, crew commander Neil Armstrong and the pilot Buzz Aldrin climbed out of the lunar module and descended onto the Sea of Tranquility. They stayed on the Moon surface for 21 hours, 36 minutes, and 21 seconds. All this time, command module pilot Michael Collins waited for them in lunar orbit.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 17 hours, 45 minutes, and 32 seconds',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 23 hours, 14 minutes, and 12 seconds',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 19 hours, 38 minutes, and 28 seconds',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 21 hours, 36 minutes, and 21 seconds',
        isCorect: true,
      },
    ],
  },
];

export const foodex = [
  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'In what country food delivery appeared?',
    answer: 'This may surprise you, but the history of food delivery as a separate market segment doesn’t have a western origin. India was the pioneer in this field. In the 19th century, the Dabbawala profession appeared – men delivered food in unique metal dishes named Dabba.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. USA',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Germany',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. France',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. India',
        isCorect: true,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'When was the first online store created?',
    answer: 'Charles Stack created the first online store in 1992. His website books.com sold books. Then, in 1994, Amazon was launched, the one we all know today, and a year later, another famous and beloved internet platform appeared – eBay.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 1989',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 1992',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 2000',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 2001',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What is the world’s best-selling product?',
    answer: 'The world’s best-selling product is petrol, yet coffee keeps up. Every year, coffee sellers earn $2 billion on this product.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Coffee',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Smartphones',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Vehicles',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Petrol',
        isCorect: true,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What is the world’s online shopping delivery record?',
    answer: 'The Chinese logistics companies managed to deliver 345 million online purchases within one day – November 14. As a result, World Shopping Day has a new sales record.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 345 mln. packages in 1 day',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 500 mln. packages in 1 week',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 200 mln. packages in 2 days',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 450 mln. packages in a month',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'How many daily visits does eBay have?',
    answer: 'Every day, eBay has 360 mln. visits and 177 mln. buyers.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. 180 mln. visits',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. 240 mln. visits',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. 360 mln. visits',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. 430 mln. visits',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },

  {
    id: uuidv4(),
    question: 'What was the first item sold online?',
    answer: 'The first safe online transaction happened on August 11, 1994. The founder of the NetMarket online marketplace, Dan Kohn, sold a compact disk to his friend. The buyer paid with a credit card.',
    options: [
      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'A. Book',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'B. Jeans',
        isCorect: false,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'C. Compact disc',
        isCorect: true,
      },

      {
        id: uuidv4(),
        option: 'D. Corn',
        isCorect: false,
      },
    ],
  },
];